sexchatster.com 2014-05-04

# Our Privacy Policy - We Care About Your Privacy! | Sexchatster

READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU AGREE, UNDERSTAND AND ACKNOWLEDGE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AS WELL AS THE TERMS OF SERVICE ON THIS WEBSITE. COME BACK TO THIS PAGE REGULARLY AS CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY BE MADE. THE NEWEST VERSION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL ALWAYS BE THE ONE THAT IS POSTED ON THIS WEBSITE.

Sexchatster values your privacy and for this reason, we have created this Privacy Policy to make you aware of the information collected when you use our website, how it is used and why we collect it. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to Sexchatster.com and it does not apply to any other website, product, service or third-party. 

By using Sexchatster.com, you agree and consent to the collection and use of data according to the terms mentioned within this Privacy Policy. We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy regularly in order to remain informed about any changes that have been made. We strongly encourage you to visit this page frequently.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Personally identifiable information such as first names, last names, email addresses, phone numbers or more may be required during registration procedures on this website. If registration is required, personally identifiable information may be collected by us. We may also record and store this information for a period of time. This information may also be recorded when you fill out forms, contact us, ask us questions of more. You have the option to not provide us with this information, but you won’t be able to benefit from our full website features and web pages if you choose not to disclose this personally identifiable information. 

We may use the personally identifiable information that is collected in order to answer questions or requests, notify you about updates or offers and also to optimize our website in order to fit better with your specific needs. This information may also be used in order to adapt advertisements to your specific interests and location. 

**Information that is Non-Personally Identifiable**

Some information is automatically collected and stored by us as well as by third parties whenever you interact with our website. Some of this information, but limited to, includes your IP address, internet browser information and operating system information. We may also collect information regarding the use of our site such as page views, links that are clicked, search queries and more. This type of information is non-personally identifiable because we have no way of knowing who you are by looking at this information. This information helps us determine the location of our users in order to target those locations with advertising and promotional offers. This information is mainly used for analysis purposes. 

A combination of your IP address, cookies and other useful information in order to identify you may be used. This is used to block, suspend or temporary prevent you from using our site if you have violated any of the rules, terms or conditions of using our website. You hereby agree that Sexchatster as well as any third-party will not be held responsible if you are blocked, suspended or terminated in the event of such violation. 

**Cookies**

Cookies will also be used on our website. These are small files that are sent to your computer’s hard drive. They pose no risks or danger to your computer and they are used mainly in order to recognize your computer every time you use our website. This speeds up your experience on our website and removes loading periods. We use cookies in order to provide you with an enhanced experience and better functionality on our website. Cookies also prevent us from having to repeatedly ask you for the same information. You can choose to block, refuse or delete cookies from within your web browser. However, if you choose to do so, you may not be able to benefit from the full features on Sexchatster.com.

**Disclosure of Information**

Sexchatster does not disclose any of the personally identifiable information that is collected from you with third parties unless required by law. This includes if the information is used to comply with legal processes, court orders or even to cooperate with law enforcement authorities. We also may disclose the personally identifiable information that we have collected in the event of a merger, acquisition or any other sale of our assets or business. 

We may disclose non-personally identifiable information with third parties such as advertisers. This information is shared as statistical information in order to know which audience to target for advertisement purposes.

We may also capture webcam images or video recordings while using Sexchatster. This is mainly captured for the monitoring of misbehaviour on our website. We may choose to store the captured images in order to improve our website. Although we monitor our website, you may still encounter users that are misbehaving. You agree to use Sexchatster.com at your own risk.

**Changing Your Personal Information**

You have the option to change your personally identifiable information at any time. If you have registered for an account, you can do so by logging into your account area on our website. If you do not have an account with us, but we still have access to personally identifiable information, you will need to contact us.

The original information that we had may still be kept or stored for purposes such as dispute resolutions, troubleshooting or even for enforcement of our agreements. For security purposes we may also require information to help verify your identity before making the changes.

**Privacy Rights for California Residents**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (“Code”) permits users of our Site who are California residents from whom we have received Personally Identifiable Information to request from us certain information regarding our disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

As stated within the code, if you request it, we will provide you with the personally identifiable information that we have collected through our site and through third parties. 

The Code allows you to control the parties with whom we share Personally Identifiable Information and the specific Personally Identifiable Information which you do not wish to be shared with those third parties. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Personally Identifiable Information you do not want us to share with third parties for direct marketing purposes. Contact us via our contact form. 

We are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through the above email address.

**Information Security**

We value your privacy which is why we take reasonable measures to ensure the security of your personally identifiable information. We protect the information and the data stored against unauthorized access.

We also limit the access to your personal information to our employees, agents or officers that need this information in order to perform their responsibilities and workload. It is important to remain aware of the fact that our website periodically requires maintenance or may experience problems which could cause breaches of security beyond our control. We cannot guarantee the security of the information on and sent from our site, and are not responsible for the acts and omissions of any third parties who receive the information. Please note that despite our best intentions, no data transmitted over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

**Links**

Sexchatster.com may contain links to other websites that are operated by our affiliates or other third parties. We are not responsible for those other websites and you must read their privacy policies and terms of service before using their websites because ours do not apply for those websites. Our privacy policy and our terms of service do not apply for any other website. You are responsible for reading through the privacy policy and terms of service of every website you visit.

**International Sharing of Information**

The personally identifiable information that is collected from Sexchatster.com may be processed and stored in the United States or in any other country in which Sexchatster.com or its affiliates operate. You consent to the transfer of your personally identifiable information outside of your own country. 

You agree to comply with all local laws, rules and regulations regarding online conduct and acceptable content. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you agree to comply with all applicable laws, rules and regulations regarding the transmission of data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside.

**Minors**

Sexchatster.com is an adult only website for people of 18 years of age or older. We do not knowingly collect data or information from minors or people under the age of 18 years old. Anyone that provides Sexchatster.com with information agrees and represents that they are at least 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you are not permitted to use, view or access our website and you must leave this site immediately. 

**Your Consent and Updates**

By using the Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version.

Updates to this privacy policy may be made from time to time. Any updates to this privacy policy will be added to this current version of the policy. The version of this privacy policy that is effective will always be the version that is posted on our website. We are not responsible for your failure to read the updates to this privacy policy. Your continued use of Sexchatster.com after such updates will be deemed acceptance of such changes. It is your responsibility to review this privacy policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so be sure to return to this page periodically to ensure familiarity with the most current version of this privacy policy. If we make changes to this privacy policy and you continue to use our website, you are agreeing to this privacy policy and any updates. We will only use personally identifiable information in accordance with the privacy policy that was in effect at the time the information was collected.

**Contacting Sexchatster**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us via our contact form.
